哦…我的颈部垫圈！
... O-oh, my head gasket.
啊 这什么鬼地方？
Eh... what the?
虎子的战舰？
The Cons' warship?
救护车 别问我怎么来的…说来话长
Ratchet? Don't ask how I got here. Long story.
救护车？听到了吗？
Ratchet? You copy?
噢 见鬼
Oh scrap!
悄悄地过去 打枪地不要…
Stealthy... stealthy...
红蜘蛛？
Starscream?
为什么每次我回到我的旧基地
Why is it that every time I return to my old stomping grounds
都能发现有汽车人在大厅里闲逛！
I find an Autobot roaming the halls?
别告诉我你爬回来找威震天了
Don't tell me you came crawling back to Megatron.
不可能！别挡路！
Hardly. Now out of my way.
小红 你得告诉我离开这里的路
Scream. You've got to show me the way off this boat.
对不起 没时间！
Sorry, too busy.
别忘了 上次你落难的时候…
Look. When you needed help...
我记得 我们是公平交易
As I recall, we bartered.
所以 除非你能提供回报
So, unless you have anything of value to offer me
否则一边去！
step aside!
立马告诉我出口！
The exit. Now!
虽然上次我放过了阿尔茜
I may have given Arcee a free pass when she and I last met!
但我也可以毫不迟疑地刺穿你 就像对飞过山一样
But I won't hesitate to skewer you as I did a certain Cliffjumper!
去死吧 隔板！
Perish, Bulkhead!
这是为了飞过山！为了大黄蜂！为了你所做的一切！
This is for Cliffjumper! For Bumblebee! For everything.
这是你逼我的…
You left me no choice...
我愿不惜一切代价再次飞起来…
Argh! What I would not give to have wings again!
啊… 跟我离开时一样
Just as I left it.
先驱号的事情终于有了转机
The Harbinger. Things are finally looking up.
噢 真的假的？！一丁点能量残渣都不剩？
Oh really!? Not one scrap of energon!
一个实验室？
A laboratory.
并且还能运作…
And it's functional.
原生体…
Protoforms?
隔板呼叫基地 发现一个很强的信号
Bulkhead to base. Picked up a strong reading.
我去调查清楚
I'm going to check it out.
让我们看看 分子内二价键连接
Let's see... Transference of binary bonding, submolecular infusion, hmm...
这个方程式很容易弄懂
The formula seems straightforward enough.
好了 我的粘土小人儿 看来你们已经准备好塑形了…
Well, my little lambs of clay, you look like alright for the molding.
…我们来个快速克隆 怎么样？
Let's give cloning a whirl, shall we?
没有活动的迹象
No sight of activity.
哈哈哈哈…
Hahahahaha...
…赐予我生命吧！
Give me a light!
啊…同志们…终于找到组织了…
Like-minded company... at last.
能量体…打包待运？
Energon? Boxed and ready for pickup?
糟了！
... Scrap!
我亲爱的成员们
Esteemed members of my armada!
你们即将见证
You now stand upon the very precipice of glory
我长久以来不懈追求的光荣时刻
to meet the destiny which I have so tenaciously worked toward.
霸天虎的领导权应该轮流坐庄！
Dynamic leadership of the Decepticons!
我…很高兴咱们达成了共识 呵呵
I am... delighted to hear that we are on the same page, heh.
我们是一体的 指挥官
We are as one, Commander.
我们分享你的记忆
We share your memories.
你的切身感受
Your very feelings.
甚至你对权力无尽的渴求!
Even your insatiable quest for power.
我知道了
I see.
很幸运 先驱号的追踪系统还能
Fortunately, The Harbinger's tracking systems
追踪到威震天的飞船
have remained synced with Megatron's warship.
当然我们要先想个办法登上去
Of course, we shall require a means of reaching the...
啊？你们能变形？
Oh! You can transform!?
你们当然能变形！
... Of course you can!
否则怎么飞到飞船上去？
How else would you fly to the ship.
我只是想考验一下 你们都通过了
That was a test which you all... eh... passed.
现在飞过去熄灭威震天那被诅咒的火种！
Now take flight and snuff Megatron's accursed Spark!
哦…我的颈部垫圈！
... O-oh, my head gasket.
散开 保持隐蔽
Spread out. Keep to the shadows.
我们中任何一人被发现都会立刻受到攻击的
Any one of us is an instant target aboard this warship.
但要是被看到我们在一起 就没有奇袭效果了
But to be seen together would sacrifice the element of surprise.
无论是谁先找到了威震天 报告你的位置
Whoever manages to find Megatron first, report your position!
红蜘蛛？
Starscream?
我迫不及待地等着欣赏威震天死亡的场面
I cannot wait to savour the vivid details of Megatron's demise...
啊
Ah!
到底怎么回事？
What is happening?!
这是为了飞过山！为大黄蜂！为了你所做的一切！
This is for Cliffjumper! For Bumblebee! For everything.
啊！
Ahhhhh...
我的遗传代码给了克隆体们我早已失去的变形齿轮！
My genetic code provides my clones with a T-cog I no longer possess
而我得到的竟是他们的痛苦？
and all I get is their agony?
通讯台！
A comm unit.
隔板呼叫基地 听到了吗？
Bulkhead to base. Do you read?
听得到吗？
Do you copy?
虎子的烂设备 就没有好使的吗？
Come on... Stupid 'Con tech! Is this thing even on?
站住！
Halt!
霸天虎信号 终于找到了！
A Decepticon beacon, at last.
忠诚的奴仆们 机会终于来了！
Devoted servants, the time has come.
为复仇而战吧
For the ultimate retribution.
擎天柱 没有隔板的消息
Optimus, no word yet from Bulkhead.
不过我监测到一些奇怪的地下信号
But I am detecting some rather curious subterranean frequencies.
地球人的吗？
Of Earthly origin?
我还不确定是什么 但我知道它的位置
I do not yet know what they are, but I do know where.
坐标是我们最后遇到威震天的地方…
The coordinates at which we last encountered Megatron.
还有毒蜘蛛
And Airachnid.
还有毒蜘蛛的机器昆虫
And Airachnid's Insecticon.
出洞吧 我的虫群们 攻击！
Arise, my armada. And attack!
我们看到的 极有可能是一次针对威震天的刺杀行动
We are in all likelihood witnessing the launch of a mission to terminate Megatron.
我想不出阻止它的理由
I can't think of a reason to stop that.
虽然我们做得到
Even if we could.
但是我们能阻止毒蜘蛛
But we can stop Airachnid.
后卫部队 向汽车人开火
Rear guard, engage the Autobots.
悄悄地过去 打枪地不要…
Stealthy... stealthy...
威震天陛下
Lord Megatron!
嗯 什么事？
Yes, what is it?
有入侵者！
An intruder.
汽车人？
Autobot?
是红蜘蛛 刚刚出现在舰桥附近
Starscream. He was last seen in vicinity of the bridge.
不！
No!
钻地 还是老把戏
Underground. There's a surprise.
威震天…是算旧账的时候了…
Megatron. It has come time to settle old scores.
哈哈哈哈 是吗 红蜘蛛? 就凭你一个人？
Hahahahaha... really, Starscream? All on your own?
事实上…
Actually...
克隆 干得不赖啊 红蜘蛛
Clones. Well-played, Starscream.
你可能根本没有跟这些喽罗一起来
If you're even here among your underlings.
喽罗？我们是一体的
Underlings? We are as one.
同时也是个军团
Though many.
把红蜘蛛的脑袋带给我
Bring me Starscream's head on a stick.
我就让你们都当我的副官
And I will reward you as my Second-in-command. All of you.
不 你在骗我们！
No! You're trying to trick us!
有吗？
Am I?
是吧?
Is he?
采纳我的提议 我们都会是赢家
Accept my proposal and we all win.
否则你们只会死于抢夺战利品的争斗之中
Otherwise, you will merely end up terminating each other to get the spoils.
毕竟那是你们的天性…
It is your nature, after all.
别听他的！
Don't listen to him!
准备死在我手上吧！
Prepare to perish at my hand!
我们的手上！
Our hands!
没错 只有我们集中火力才能确保威震天被消灭
Yes! Only our combined firepower will assure Megatron's destruction.
准备！
Take aim!
你们听到了吗？
Do you hear that?
别管它 数到3就开火！
Ignore! Fire on three!
1 2
One. Two!
刚才是什么声音？
What was that?
翻盘的声音
The sound of the tables turning.
那上面发生了什么？
What is going on up there?
前三次摧毁你还是很惬意的
Exterminating you was so gratifying the first three times!
毒蜘蛛？刺客们今天赶集吗？
Airachnid. A busy day for assassins.
阿尔茜
Arcee!
当你熄灭我火种的时候 做得痛苦点
When you extinguish my Spark, make it hurt.
你知道我会对你下更重的手
You know: I would extend the courtesy to you.
我可不像你
I'm not like you.
很好…
Very well.
不！
No!
原谅我们 真正的主人
Forgive us, one true Lord and Master.
今天南辕北辙的事真是够多了
This day has certainly seen its share of thwarted intentions.
无论如何 我都要离开这艘破船！
One way or another, I'm getting off this boat!
又怎么了！
Now what?!
好狗不挡道！
Out of my way!
我的君王 我们的动力设备被破坏了
My Liege! Our power core has been compromised.
准备着陆…
Prepare for landing.
休眠状态 便宜她了
Stasis. She deserves worse.
我的原计划可不会这么温柔 你想象不到的
I intended worse. More times than you know.
你的这一选择 会让你变得更为强大
You are stronger for the choice you made.
伙计们 你们绝对想不到我这一天的经历！
Guys, you're not gonna believe the day I had!
你也是 嗯？
You too, huh?
红蜘蛛陛下 您最忠实的仆人回来了
Lord Starscream! Your most loyal servant has returned.
但我很遗憾地通知您 我们的任务失败了
But I regret to inform you that our collective mission has failed.
嗯 没错 我感觉到了
Hmm, yes. I got that sense.
因为我疼得苦不堪言
Something to do with a throbbing ache in my side!
你知道我要杀了你？
You... knew I would attempt to terminate you...
我感受到了你的痛苦 真的
Ah... I feel your pain. Really I do.
啊！见鬼 好疼呀！
Arrrgh! Scrap that hurt!